Nick Gashkov, Software Engineer

http://gashkov.com

2+ years of industry experience with strong knowledge of back-end web technologies such as Python (Django) to build RESTful APIs and front-end frameworks such as Vue and React. In addition to websites, I have developed various scripts and utilities, data science services with numpy, pandas and desktop applications with PyQt.

SKILLS

- Python: stdlib, numpy, pandas, PyQt, Celery, Django, XLSX/DOCX/PDF generation.
- JS: Webpack, Babel, Vue.js, Vuex.
- Django: ORM, CBV, templates, queries optimization, Django REST Framework.
- CSS: Sass, Flex, Bulma.io.
- **HTML**: HTML 5, SEO.
- PostgreSQL: Indices, transactions, views.
- Caching: Redis, Memcache.
- Ops: Nginx, Gunicorn, Supervisord, Ansible.
- **Git**: Merge requests, gitflow.
- LaTeX: Documentation.

EXPERIENCE

Netrika

Saint Peterburg, Russia
Nov 2016 - Present

Email: nick@gashkov.com

Mobile: +7-999-249-7828

Software Engineer

Output

Nov 2016 - Present

Development and deployment: Maintained several projects from planning stage to deployment. Mainly worked with Django and Django REST Framework.

EDUCATION

ITMO University

Bachelor of Engineering in Electrical and Electronics

Saint Petersburg, Russia

2014 - 2019